Guide to the Ralph Rydholm papers, 1936-2014 and undated RL.11279
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Print Materials, 1958-2014 and undated; 2
  - Charlie Larson--Internal Branding Seminar, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Chicago '76 Awards, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Chicago '79 Awards, 1979 (Box 25)
  - Chicago! Special Advertising Section, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Chicago Area Boy Scouts Dinner for William L. Weiss, 1994 (Box 25)
  - Chicago High School for the Arts Board Handbook, 2009 (Box 25)
  - Chicago High School for the Arts ChiArts Inaugural, 2009 (Box 25)
  - Chicago High School for the Arts Graduation, 2014 (Box 25)
  - Chicago Museum of Sports, 2001 (Box 25)
  - Chicago Public Education Fund--Annual Report, 2000 (Box OV10)
  - Chicago Public Education Fund--Better Schools Are Everybody's Business, circa 2002 (Box 25)
  - The Chicago Show, 1994, 1996; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Clio '86, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Copy Development Process, 1994 (Box 26)
  - David Olson (Leo Burnett)--Creative Management of the Creative Product, circa 1994 (Box 26)
  - ECS--Effective Presentation Skills, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Famous Music Corporation--Famous Favorites A Select List of Songs, 1961-1963 (Box 26)
  - First Take Magazine, 1981-1985 (Box 26)
  - Flash vol. 7 no. 1 (Rydholm interview), 1989 (Box 26)
  - Gallagher Report, 1988 (Box 26)
  - GATX Survey of Your Company's Distribution Facilities, circa 1965 (Box OV10)
  - Herbert Moser--Auch Morgen Ist Wieder Ein Heute [Tomorrow Another Day Will Come. In German], 1986 (Box 26)
  - Indiana University Marketing Club Advertising Seminar, 1986 (Box 26)
  - Institute of Practitioners of Advertising--Review of Current Practice Brand Evaluation (David Haigh), 1996 (Box 26)
  - International Broadcasting Awards, 1970-1987; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - IOA Outdoor Newsletter vol. 4 no. 7, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Island Melee, 1998 (Box 26)
  - Jacques Seguela--Demain Il Sera Trop Star, 1989 (Box 27)
  - James Webb Young--A Technique for Producing Ideas [In Japanese; note to Rydholm from Don Johnston], undated (Box 27)
  - John D.C. Little--Models and Managers: The Concept of a Decision Calculus, 1970 (Box 27)
  - John Robert Rieben (U. Wisconsin-Madison)--The Rise and Fall (and maybe rise again) of American Advertising, 1995 (Box 27)
  - Judicial Council of California--Task Force on Jury System Improvements Final Report, 2004 (Box 27)
  - Judie Lannon and Peter Cooper--Humanistic Advertising, 1983 (Box 27)
  - JWT--Ad Age centennial tribute, 1964 (Box OV10)
  - JWT newsletters and publications, 1971-1986; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT Worldwide Creative Forum, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Leo Burnett--The Marlboro Story, 1958 (Box 27)
  - Lowenbrau point of sale, undated (Box 27)
  - Lowenbrau--This World Calls for...Lowenbrau, 1985 (Box 27)
  - Lowenbrau World, 1985 (Box 27)
  - Madison Avenue--Salute to Michigan Avenue, 1986 (Box OV10)
  - Marketing Science Institute--Market-Based Assets and Shareholder Value (Srivastava et al.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - Martin Mayer--Madison Avenue USA, 1958 (Box 28)
  - Mary Wells Lawrence--A Big Life, 2002 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and newsprint, 1980-1997 (Box OV11)
  - MPA--American Magazine Conference, 1990 (Box 28)
  - MPA Kelly Awards, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Nationwide--Pro Football Hall of Fame Enshrinees Civic Dinner, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Northwestern Magazine (Rydholm obituary), 2014 (Box 28)
  - Og Mandino--The Greatest Salesman in the World, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Viewpoint, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Post Keyes Gardner--Post Scripts, 1963 (Box 28)
  - Radio Hall of Fame, 1994 (Box 28)
  - Roux Seguela Cayzac & Goudard: 20 ans, toujours 20 ans (RSCG 20th anniversary), 1990 (Box OV10)
  - SAM (Serving Advertising in the Midwest), 1970-1972 (Box 28)
  - Screen, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
  - Sounds of Nostalgia, 1973 (Box 28)
  - Sterling (Red) Quinlan--Quinlan's Key, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Tatham's Half Century--Ad Age tribute feature, 1996 (Box OV10)
  - The Tavern Club--The Barfly vol. ix no. 4, 1991 (Box 29)
  - Tim Galfas party invitation, undated (Box 29)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau--Conference Speeches, 1969 (Box 29)
  - V for Victory--Hoover Remembers World War II exhibit brochure, 1991 (Box 29)
  - Wall Street Journal Creative Leaders, 1993 (Box OV10)
  - WFYR Top 2000 Oldies, undated (Box 29)
  - Who's Who in America Vol. 2 1980-1981 (Rydholm has entry) (Box 29)
  - Will Howard--Creative Targeting, 1997 (Box 29)
  - Young Executives Club News vol. 5 no. 3, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Charles Goodrum and Helen Dalrymple--Advertising in America the First 200 Years, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Off the Street Club--Where Happy Endings Begin, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
  - Pub Award Annual, 1983 (Box 30)
  - The Struggle to Get Ahead--The International Andy Awards, 1996 (Box 30)
  - Tatham--Poster portfolio, undated [Includes Oak Street Council, Sheer Indulgence, Naturalizer) (Box 30)
  - Allan J. Cox--Confessions of a Corporate Headhunter, 1973 (Box 30a)
  - Allan Cox--Straight Talk for Monday Morning, 1990 (Box 30a)
  - Peter Georgescu--The Source of Success, 2005 (Box 30a)
  - Sterling (Red) Quinlan--Quinlan's Key, 1984 (Box 30a)
- Artifacts and Memorabilia, 1936-2000 and undated; 3
  - General Items, 1936-2000 and undated; 15
    - Boggle Manual Digital Calculator, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Camel cigarette advertisement, 1936 (Box OV1)
    - Childhood--Pins, badges, etc., circa 1945-1954 (Box 31)
    - Clapboard--Chicago Film Council, 1981 (Box OV12)
    - Fingerweight--Speed Weights, 2000 (Box 31)
    - Hoover Windtunnel replica/tape measure, undated (Box 31)
    - JWT 1980 Spring Olympics medal (Box 31)
    - Military service (U.S. Air Force)--Insignia, etc., 1958-1959 (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous pins, badges, medals, etc., undated (Box 31)
    - Schlitz--Rubik's Cube, undated (Box 31)
  - Awards, 1936-2000 and undated; 16
    - AAAA--Atlanta Council, 1997 (Box 32)
    - Ad Age Creative Workshop, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Ad Week, 1992 (Box 32)
    - BBDO--Calm Deodorant, Maillol drawing on tile, undated (Box 32)
    - Cannes Silver Lion, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Chicago Public Education Fund, undated (Box 32)
    - Clio, undated (Box 32)
    - IOA Award, Juror Appreciation, 1969 (Box 32)
    - JWT owl relief in clay: JWT '85 Awards Metro Museum, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Wall Street Journal Creative Leaders, 1996 (Box 32)
    - Young Executives Club, 1993 (Box 32)
  - Clothing and Textiles, 1936-2000 and undated; 17
    - Apron--Super Bowl XX, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Austin Times "A" jacket letter, circa 1954 (Box 33)
    - Bandana--Hoover New Horizons, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Bandana--J. Walter Reindeer Roundup, undated (Box 33)
    - Bandana--WLS-TV Circle 7 Roundup, undated (Box 33)
    - Bomber Jacket--JWT Chicago, undated (Box 33)
    - Hat--JWT Kazoo Band, undated (Box 33)
    - Schlitz knitted item, undated (Box 33)
    - Sweatshirt--Oscar Mayer Meatpackers, undated (Box 33)
    - T-Shirt--EURO RSCG (two versions), undated (Box 33)
    - T-Shirt--Finger Weights (Box 33)
    - T-Shirt--FM98 AM 1000 Loop Athletic Club, undated (Box 33)
    - T-Shirt--Lions '96, 1996 (Box 33)
    - T-Shirt--We Make a Mean Lean Cuisine, undated (Box 33)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1962-2009 and undated; 4
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies. Address by Joseph P. Nacchio. 93AAAA-090, 1993 April 21-24. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-001)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies. Advertising's Role in Building Brand Equity. 93AAAA-030. 1993 April 21-24. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-002)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies. Advertising's Role in Building Brand Equity. 93AAAA-030. 1993 April 21-24. Larry Light. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-003)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies. Client Panel: If Only Agencies Would. 4A's Management Conference/Annual Meeting, April 9-11. 97AAAA-210., 1997 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-004)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies. When the Inmates Run the Asylum. 4A's April 21-24 1993. 93AAAA-020. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-005)
  - Amy Landecker. Was It Something I Said?, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-006)
  - Amy Landecker. Was It Something I Said?, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-007)
  - Arthur Laffer. Growth vs. Redistribution: Which Course for the 80s?, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-008)
  - Bank Marketing Association Creative Overview Keynote Address., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-009)
  - Chicken & Biscuits 3 (We're Really Cooking). :30. Tatham/RSCG Att. Karen Wallisky., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-010)
  - Cumberland River Gang #1, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-011)
  - Dan Williams Music 1995 presentation tape. Corona Light; Bud "Boxing Gandhi's"; Busch Beer; Long John Silver's; Dodge Blues Medley "Levon Helm; Buddy Guy and Junior Wells;"; Bud "Rock Solid"; FTD; Miller "Lee Roy Parnell"; Harvey's Bristol Cream; Bud "Joe Diffie"; Toyota; Ponderosa; Clorox "Mama's Got the Magic"; Red Lobster theme. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-012)
  - Dan Williams Music 1995 presentation tape. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-013)
    Corona Light; Bud "Boxing Gandhi's"; Busch Beer; Long John Silver's; Dodge Blues Medley "Levon Helm; Buddy Guy and Junior Wells;"; Bud "Rock Solid"; FTD; Miller "Lee Roy Parnell"; Harvey's Bristol Cream; Bud "Joe Diffie"; Toyota; Ponderosa; Clorox "Mama's Got the Magic"; Red Lobster theme.
  - Dole Pineapple, Ted Bates 3-9-87, 1987 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-014)
  - Dr. J. Clayton Lafferty--Management Style, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-015)
  - Dr. Julian Jaynes--The Origins of Human Creativity, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-016)
  - Hardee's spots 10/25/93. Klaff/Weinstein., 1993 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-017)
  - Hardee's P1, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-018)
  - Tatham RSCG. Hardee's; 93/10/28 SV3280 audiocassette dub., 1993 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-019)
    Big Campaign. :60 Full Music; :30 Full Music; Big Difference :60 Radio; Big Secret :60 Radio; Big Promo #1 :60 Radio; Big Promo #2 :60 Radio
  - Jeremy Bullmore, JWT London; Goodbye Mr. Chips, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-020)
  - Labatt's Crystal. Summer Nights; The Same; New Wave., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-021)
  - Lady Luck comp :30, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-022)
  - Letting Go., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-023)
  - Lisa Barnett. Prisoner of Your Own Heart, 1989 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-024)
    Prisoner of Your Own Heart; A Place Between; Just Give Me Some Time; Love Stories; Why Must I Chase Dreams of You? Old Kentucky Friends; Do You Ever Dream of Me? If I'm So Easy to Love (Why Am I So Easy to Leave?); Love Lullaby for Two.
  - Lotto. Sorry 60; Routine 60, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-025)
  - Lowenbrau audio, 1985 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-026)
  - Macrose Music presentation reel., 1992 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-027)
    Northwest Air "Some People"; Bell Atlantic "Take Six"; Fox TV "Roc's Title Theme"; Seagram's "Cooler World"; Bell Atlantic "Sundays"/"Joe Hendricks"/"The Spinners"; Clarion "It's Hip"; Kodak "Azul"/'Mike Tyson"; Ultress "Blair Brown"
  - Mary Pat Hutton (JWT Chicago) 35th Anniversary., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-028)
  - Mary Pat Hutton (JWT Chicago) 35th Anniversary., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-029)
  - Momma's. Klaff/Weinstein., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-030)
  - Momma's. Klaff/Weinstein., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-031)
  - Momma's. All vox 12/13/93. Klaff/Weinstein., 1993 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-032)
  - Momma's. No lead vox 12/13/93. Klaff/Weinstein., 1993 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-033)
  - Momma's. No vox 12/13/93. Klaff/Weinstein., 1993 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-034)
  - Newberry Library. Shopping Alternative :30 Radio 11/10/92 Mix., 1992 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-035)
  - Northwestern 17, Notre Dame 15. September 2 1995 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-036)
  - Old Spice 3 TV DRMES. Klaff/Weinstein, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-037)
  - Orson Welles session script, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-038)
  - Prudential "Like a Rock", Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-039)
  - Ralph Rydholm speech. Advertising Club of the Virgin Islands March 17th and march 18th 1998 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-040)
  - Reel 1 1:50-3:50 10-7-85 JTB, 1985 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-041)
  - Ron Chancey Productions Demonstration Reel., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-042)
    Chevy, Bob Seger; Geo instrumental; Ford, Tabatha Fare; Pepsi, Jessica Boucher; Marlboro instrumental; Chevy, Billy Yates; McDonald's, Joy White; 7-Up, Dana McVicker; Ford, T. Graham Brown; McDonald's, Jennifer Warnes.
  - Schlitz., Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-043)
  - 1982 Schlitz presentation JWT. (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-044)
    Gusto is Here; The Gusto Makes It Work; Shake Hands with Gusto; The Night is for Gusto; Schlitz Right Now; Gusto Means Schlitz; Hot Times, Cold Schlitz; Schlitz Beer Mug; What a Head, What a Body; Schlitz Goes On and On
  - Southern Writers Group. Gary Version--Flash; JWT Song--Dylan, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-045)
  - Starburst "Start Up the Juice" w/announcer, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-046)
  - Time, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-047)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-048)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-049)
  - Wally's "5109", Undated (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-050)
  - Lowenbrau: This World Calls for Lowenbrau radio campaign demo only, 1985 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11279-CS-051)
    Contemporary; Contemporary with Donut; Rhythm and Blues; Rock/Young Adult; Platform/Contemporary long copy; International Hispanic; Alemannia Hispanic; USA Hispanic. 8:30
  - J. Walter Thompson Creative Reel 9/1/99. Chicago Office., 1999 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-001)
    Miracle Whip Flavors "Garlic"; Nabisco Air Crisps "Hey"; Polly-O "Pizza Agent Man"; Butterfinger "Two of a Kind"; Blockbuster "War Wounds"; Miracle Whip "Knife"; Partnership for a Drug-Free America "Not an Addict"; Triscuit "You're a Man"; Kraft "Sitting Down"; Blockbuster "Lunch/Scooper"; Miracle Whip "Tweety"; Nabisco Air Crisps "500 Easy Pieces"
  - J. Walter Thompson "You Don't Have to Yell to Sell" Retail Realities: Our thoughts on acquiring and retaining retail clients, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-002)
  - Leading the Way: The Saga of a Viking Ship. Euro RSCG Tatham. American Scandinavian Council/Viking World Museum. Master (script included) 4/23/97. 5:50, 1997 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-003)
  - Marrakech. 3/4" NBC. Gable & Greenstreet "Hucksters"; "Crazy People" Volvo and Metamucil ads, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-004)
  - NARC, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-005)
  - Ralph Rydholm Four A's Presentation. Film clip montage; Heilbronner; People; Film quotes; Moscow on the Hudson, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-006)
  - Ralph Rydholm Four A's Presentation., Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-007)
    Film clip montage; Heilbronner; People; Film quotes; Moscow on the Hudson
  - Ted Bates Advertising presentation reel 14 spots. Dub May 15, 1986. TSN (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-008)
    Warner-Lambert Dentyne "Telephone Booth" Certs "Breathless"; Colgate CDC "Generation"; Effem Foods M&M "Chocolate and Peanut" Uncle Ben's "Man and Woman"; Nissan "Eyes" "Son of Stanza"; Liver Foundation "Classroom"
  - Untitled "Cougar"?, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11279-Umatic-009)
  - Pan American Air. "Swing" :60 Client Master #2. 2/28/74, 1974 (Box AV2, Video-reel RL11279-VID2-001)
  - Hancock. JWT edit Chicago 12489, Undated (Box AV2, Film-reel RL11279-F35-001)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11279-F35-002)
  - Carlos Donato Trio Live, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-001)
  - Carlos Donato Trio; Look for Tomorrow. Mono dub of stereo 8-track cartridge. TRT 38:09., 1979 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-002)
  - Dorado tracks. 23 pack (old); 100 mm (new), Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-003)
  - Hamm's Beer, J. Walter Thompson. Mono masters. Be What You Want to Be :60, 1976 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-004)
  - Hamm's presentation master tape., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-005)
    Hamm's and Coors; One Whole Lot of Beer; Then Came Hamm's; Ingredient Presenter; Hamm's Lets You Have It; Ingredient Land.
  - Hamm's Radio :60 lengths. Movie Hits; Parade; Heritage Road. Master., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-006)
  - Happy Birthday Ralph from Kelso Herston, 1985 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-007)
  - Jack Clement Recording Studios. Florence Warner. "One Last Love Song"; "Soul Deep"; Old-Fashioned Love." (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-008)
  - Johnny Western and the Sons of the Pioneers. Mono dub of stereo 8-track cartridge. TRT 33:13., 1979 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-009)
  - Marcene Harris, jazz vocalist., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-010)
  - Neil Diamond. Love at the Greek. Off TV., 1977 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-011)
  - Radio Spots., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-012)
    Old Milwaukee; Allied Van; Enden; Orange Crush; Schlitz Malt Liquor; Taystee Brand; Borden's; Wrigley.
  - Radio Spots., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-013)
    Allied Van; Taystee; Armour; Borden's.
  - Singers Unlimited Christmas, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-014)
  - Speech, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-015)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-016)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-017)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-018)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-019)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-020)
  - Wash Sq. Enden. Ralph and Rube., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-021)
  - Introducing Air Corps :30, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-022)
  - Flo's single, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-023)
  - Florence Warner mono copy. Set 1 Atlanta stuff, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-024)
  - Gillette, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-025)
    Handler. Hamilton Comp. Stud Look; Bird's Nest; Bed. :60 and :30.
  - Goin' Down to Nashville master tails, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-026)
  - Hamm's Beer, J. Walter Thompson. Honest Beer :60 and :30, 1971 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-027)
  - Hamm's Beer. The Thing to Be Is What You Are., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-028)
  - Helene Curtis Enden. "Two Shampoos"., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-029)
    Rigoletto; Better Half; Washington Square; Everybody; Movie Trailer; Stout Hearted Men. Produced by Edward H. Weiss & Co.
  - J. Walter Thompson radio reel., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-030)
    Hamm's Beer; Wild Drums; Wild Bass Drum; Swinging Body; Kraft. Mono
  - Kelso Herston Super Brunette music dub, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-031)
  - Nowhere, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-032)
  - Old Milwaukee; "I Like Beer" track 29. Safety tape; produced by Post-Keyes-Gardner., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-033)
  - Orange Crush (old)., 1964 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-034)
    Abandoned Jungle; Party; Struck Twister; Phone Booth; Enden. Produced by Edward H. Weiss. AR-1384-2-24-64.
  - Orange Crush Clark Lonely. Thirst Crusher radio spot, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-035)
  - Pan Am Kelso Herston Productions., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-036)
    Experimental music; Folk; Country rock.
  - Pan Am Kelso Herston Productions., 1973 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-037)
    Experimental music; Folk; Country rock. J. Walter Thompson Company. 10/2/73.
  - Ralph Rydholm speech to Houston, Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-038)
  - Schlitz. Project M composite :60 TV trk.12. U-18998. Produced by Post-Keyes-Gardner., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-039)
  - Steve Goodman., Undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-040)
  - Taystee Bread "Flavor First"; Allied Van "Give a Call" "When You Move", Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-041)
  - Tex Ritter., Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-042)
  - Tom Hall's Going Away Party, Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-043)
  - Tribute--Ralph Rydholm, Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-044)
  - Wrigley experimental, Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-045)
  - Right Time #1872. U-50537, J. Walter Thompson Company, 1971 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-046)
    Apple Stripteaser; Apple Picking Time; Tropical Suit; Tropical Dorothy. May 1971.
  - Right Time #1872. U-50537, J. Walter Thompson Company., 1971 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-047)
  - Ralph Rydholm tribute. Written, created, directed and voiced by Alan Keys, Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-048)
  - Right Time. Any Time; Middle of the Road; Bothwell, Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-049)
  - Simonize radio., 1967 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-050)
    Announcer Man; Spring is Here; Women Drivers; Wax the Smoke. 8/25/67
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11279-RR-051)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-001)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-002)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-003)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-004)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-005)
  - Hair Color--Look of Natural, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-006)
  - Hancock edit JWT Chicago, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-007)
  - Nowhere/Look of Natural, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-008)
  - untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-009)
  - Taystee Tender Twist ttt-60-317. 16mm comp b/w ans print. 4-5-63, 1963 (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-010)
  - J. Walter Thompson commercials. Slow Motion; Alive #1; Alive #2., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-011)
  - ITT Thorp "Farmer", Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-012)
  - KenL Ration "Shoes" KM-30-227, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-013)
  - Join the Swing. AVSB-1023. 30-sec., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-014)
  - Blondes, American Style; Blonde Country. 700069. K953., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-015)
  - Bug, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-016)
  - Compactor, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-017)
  - Compactor, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-018)
  - Crowd Stopper, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-019)
  - Earthborn 30-sec., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-020)
  - Enden "Two Shampoos" EN-EXP-23-30. 15", Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-021)
  - Family of Problems, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-022)
  - Kodak "Engage Party" EKIC-7973. 04618--01., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-023)
  - KenL Ration "Newspaper" RM--30-225-30 sec., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-024)
  - KenL Ration "Shoes" KM-60-403-60 sec., Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-025)
  - "People Don't" out, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-026)
  - Simonize "Submarine" :30 first trial (too dark), Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-027)
  - Toothpaste, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-028)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Converted, Table Top" 1353-60, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-029)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Converted, Table Top" 1300-30, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-030)
  - Uncle Ben's Rice "Flavour'd Rice, Table Top" 1302-30 new, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-031)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box AV4, Film-reel RL11279-F16-032)